[Longwan Village, Hanzhou City, 2005]
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Xiaoshuai?
What are you doing here? Why not come in?
I...
Wait. Why did you come out?
For some fresh air,
since I had too many drinks.
Check out what I bought you.
What is it?
"What is it?" A gift it is.
Just this one?
How many more do you want?
Alright.
Congratulations.
I'd better call you Officer Wen
from now on.
Cut it out.
Listen,
we'll be best buddies forever.
Even when we're old and gray,
I'll still be Bo,
and you'll still be Xiaoshuai.
Got it?
Can you stop with this mushy stuff?
I'm telling you,
I'm not sure
if I'll still be this handsome by then,
but you surely won't be.
What, you think you won't age, huh?
If I lose my looks, you'll lose yours too.
Stop it. It sounds terrible.
So you do know it sounds terrible.
[The Punishment]
[Punish those who commit crimes
and make mistakes]
[so as to discipline them,]
[and execute those
who violate the prohibitions]
[so as to terrify would-be violators.]
[Guanzi – On Laws and Standards]
[Episode 26]
Tianye.
The police have traced the money
we gave Mrs. Wen and Bo.
It was He Biao.
He Biao must've tipped them off.
As I told you before,
we should've informed Mrs. Wen and Bo
beforehand.
Now, look what has happened.
They
haven't got to spend a penny of it.
We've even got Bo in a heap of trouble.
Now, think about
how we're going to explain to Mrs. Wen.
This is my fault.
My recklessness caused Bo trouble.
I'll be responsible,
explain everything,
and state that the money has nothing to do
with Mrs. Wen and Bo.
Who are you going to say that to?
Are you able to clear their names?
Then what do you suggest?
If Bo's really jeopardized by us
and lose his job
as a police officer,
how can we face Jiangyong
and his wife?
S-So what if he loses his job?
It's not that big of a deal.
Worst case, he can join us.
Liu Tianfei! Do you even hear yourself?
What's all this yelling for?
Bo and Mrs. Wen
didn't know about the money at all.
What's our priority now?
It's to keep them from figuring out
our real business.
Tianye,
there are still some goods around.
We must quickly remove them
and clean the mess,
especially the cash in the cold storage.
How to transfer them?
Contact Uncle Limin.
There are empty warehouses
at the port he manages.
It's safer there.
Mrs. Wen's calling.
[Incoming: Mrs. Wen]
Mrs. Wen.
The procuratorate called me.
I demand an explanation.
That money...
was meant for you and Bo.
But since you refused it,
I saved it up for you.
What gave you the right to do so?
You've got Bo in hot water! You know that?
Don't you know why I never used
that money?
Mrs. Wen,
I'm sorry.
But rest assured.
We promise to keep Bo from harm.
Jiangyong
had a share in that money too, so...
You even have the nerve
to mention Jiangyong!
Mrs. Wen,
actually...
the money is not dirty.
We just wanted you and Bo
to have a better life.
We were doing fine without that money.
If you truly want the best for Bo,
then keep a distance from him.
Get as far away as you can!
Tianye.
Come in here with me.
[House of Benevolence]
Kneel.
Kneel!
[House of Benevolence]
Tianye,
today, before our ancestors,
answer my questions honestly.
Now, tell me,
where did the money you gave Bo come from?
The profits of Longwan Logistics.
Tianye,
it's been less than 3 years
since you thought of
founding this company till this moment.
Now you're saying that you spared as much
as 5 million for Bo from your profits.
How are we supposed to believe that?
Over the past 3 years,
we've truly caught the logistics boom.
Everyone has made good money.
So I,
Peng, Taoyi, and Tianfei
contributed some of our earnings,
plus dividends
from several other companies,
[House of Benevolence]
and pooled them together
to make up this 5 million.
Jiangyong...
was one of Longwan Logistics' founders.
He didn't get to live a good life.
[In Memory of the Liu Family's Ancestors]
So we wanted to improve the lives
[In Memory of the Wen Family's Ancestors]
[In Memory of the Qin Family's Ancestors]
of his wife and son.
That's all.
Is this money clean?
Yes.
Are you sure?
I am sure, Mom.
I just don't get it.
In only 3 years,
Longwan Logistics
has soared to such heights like a rocket.
Have you really not done anything shady?
What don't you understand, Mom?
What makes you doubt me? As I told you,
these few years are golden times
for logistics business.
Besides, I said a long time ago
that Longwan could produce high profits.
Why did everyone target this land?
Because they saw the potential in it.
Am I wrong for using it
to make money myself?
No, you're not wrong.
Making money isn't wrong.
We the Longwan people have always
been upright in character and conduct.
Listen,
if you make money by dirty means—
be it for the good of Longwan—
you'll end up reaping bitter fruit!
Son, you...
You're destroying Longwan
and leading it down a path of no return
with what you're doing now!
Since when...
Since when have you become
completely different?
[House of Benevolence]
Mom.
The time has come
to save Longwan Logistics.
Issue a notice
that a shareholders' meeting
will be held in a few days.
Mom...
[Ancestral Hall
of the Liu, Wen, and Qin Families]
[House of Benevolence]
Your actions had better align
with your declaration
to compensate Jiangyong,
so he'd rest in peace.
It doesn't matter
if you're rich or poor.
Just don't take the wrong path.
[House of Benevolence]
[Incoming: He Biao]
Liu Tianye.
Longwan Logistics has made the news.
Are you okay?
You called me so soon.
Why not worry about your brother instead?
Let's skip that crap.
Without my approval,
you'll never make it to the inner circle.
I don't care if I'll make it that far.
But if you dare target my family,
I'll definitely ruin everything for you.
Liu Tianye.
Thank you.
I've been acting as Muzhi for so long.
Today, I finally get to be Biao again.
Tianye.
Madam Wen plans to hold
a shareholders' meeting.
A shareholders' meeting?
What is she up to?
My mother intends
to kick us all out of the corporation.
Well...
What should we do?
She's canvassing shareholders.
We can do that too.
That's not the most urgent issue now.
The allegations against Longwan Logistics
have gone viral.
Our cooperation with Xinrui
must be paused.
That's what He Biao wants.
If we hit the brakes,
he'll get a chance to swoop in.
What?
Hasn't he admitted defeat
as he's already doomed?
Is he still dreaming of
turning the tables?
Tell our people to get prepared.
Cut ties with those subsidiary companies.
The police will track them down soon.
Got it.
Any news about He Gang?
We've searched every hospital in the city.
No trail of him at all.
Could he have fled?
Anyway,
if he doesn't have his wounds treated,
he'll definitely die.
As I recall, He Biao knows Dr. Chen
from the City Second Hospital.
Right.
Exactly.
They know each other.
Dr. Chen is a freeloader
and a gambler,
who has lost a lot of money
at He Biao's place.
Why not ask him,
now that we can't find He Gang?
I remember Dr. Chen has
a thing for...
Zhou Sisi.
[Hanzhou Public Security]
Qin Feng...
I've supervised him for 2 years,
and Wen Bo for quite some time too.
Whatever cases they handled,
they never complained,
even in the face of hardships.
I have faith in them.
I don't believe
they'd yield to temptation.
Doubtlessly,
they're good officers.
But good officers might also take bribes.
It happened before within the system.
So, I suggest
in a time like this,
we must...
conduct a thorough investigation.
We have to uncover the truth
and clear our comrades' names.
In addition,
shall we...
temporarily reassign officers
who are in sensitive situations?
Are you suggesting...
Qin Feng should be reassigned?
It's a suggestion
open for discussion.
As it happens,
Ganghang Public Security Bureau
has always wanted to have him over.
I think this is
a perfect opportunity.
For one thing,
Ganghang Bureau will be stronger
with him onboard.
For another thing, to him,
it's a change of environment and mindset.
The main purpose
to calm
public sentiment.
Who else would like to speak?
Director Ye,
may I have the floor?
Sure. Go ahead.
Qin Feng is just a precinct captain.
What's the point of transferring him?
I'm head
of the Criminal Investigation Unit.
It should be me,
if anyone is to be transferred.
We did attempt to transfer you there,
but you were extremely reluctant,
weren't you?
From where I stand,
Longwan Logistics' matter
is not necessarily connected
to Qin Feng and Wen Bo.
Such a thing is happening
as we're halfway through
the investigation on the He brothers.
Someone is clearly trying to sabotage it.
What does this indicate?
It indicates we're on the right track.
Now, if Qin Feng is transferred
just over some negative buzz,
how are we supposed to
proceed with the investigation?
Should we even continue with it?
We've been police officers for many years,
working our tails off,
putting in overtime,
and sacrificing our health.
We battle criminals on a daily basis
with our wits and courage.
What's it all for?
What lies before us now
is a complex social network.
Hanzhou is just a small place.
It's normal for people there
to be connected or related.
But I can assure you
that we've handled every matter
by the book.
For what?
Just for fulfilling our duties, right?
Zhong, don't get so agitated.
It sounds like
you're refuting me.
I just want the best for the case.
If you truly care about these officers,
you should be supportive of their work
and...
Alright. Enough.
It's my belief
that the investigation
must not stop.
Zhong,
aren't there many other officers
in your unit?
Make sure you reassure
everyone.
Yes.
Be flexible with the approach.
But
don't be swayed by public opinion.
We need to neutralize
the negative social impact
and strive for
people's trust.
Most importantly,
we must get things done.
Yan,
what's your opinion?
Well...
I'll say a few words then?
So far,
the matter
has escalated
and caused
an extremely negative social impact.
The credibility
of the Municipal Bureau
and even the entire police force
are being questioned.
There isn't a single positive comment
online!
However the investigation will turn out,
we must quickly quell the public outcry.
[Hanzhou Public Security]
First,
get in contact
with whoever posted
the whistleblower materials
to verify if the content is true
and if there's any defamation.
Second,
disclose investigation progress
to the public soon,
so as to demonstrate our credibility
and also...
our sincerity.
Third,
respond
with decisive action.
The Municipal Bureau will fully cooperate
with all anti-smuggling operations.
We'll launch a formal investigation
on Longwan Logistics.
Besides,
as for what was mentioned about Qin Feng
and Wen Bo,
I suggest
they be
suspended.
Consider it a vacation for them.
When the results come out,
we'll discuss further.
Director Ye, what do you think?
[Hanzhou Public Security]
I agree.
Meeting adjourned.
-Captain Zhong.
What will happen to them?
Captain Zhong,
it's impossible.
The two of them are by no means
involved in any shady stuff.
We can all vouch for them.
That's right.
Wen Bo is such a good kid.
How could he have possibly taken bribes?
Someone's clearly trying to sabotage him!
Rest assured.
I'll fight anyone
who's after him to the end.
I'm determined to protect him!
That's my word.
Also,
aren't there people
trying to obstruct our investigation?
Let's put as much effort as we can
into probing
till the truth is out!
If you need help, come to me anytime.
How dare anyone touches my people?
I'll show them what happens!
Is he...
really your mentor?
Yes, I guess.
Guys,
Captain Zhong has stepped up.
Look,
Bo often treated us to boba tea,
didn't he?
Captain Qin and Bo
are just temporarily away.
I believe justice will be restored
for them in time.
What should we do now?
Now, we should do as much as we can
to help them both weather through
these difficult times.
Can we do it?
Absolutely!
Let's get started!
Yes!
Impressive.
You're starting to look like Mentor.
It's time to show my true abilities.
[Hanzhou Public Security Bureau]
Nice and slow.
I know.
Alright.
Mentor,
please stay for dinner.
Take a seat.
I'll go cook.
Just wait for 10 minutes.
Where are those...
pickles of yours? Serve some to Mentor.
Those are from ages ago.
They must've gone bad
as I was hospitalized for a long time.
I should throw them away.
I really mean it.
I'm going home.
My wife's waiting for me
to have dinner with her.
I cook really fast.
Ten minutes is all I need.
I'd rather leave.
Hey.
What was that about?
How old is he now?
What do you want him to do?
Tell me.
I didn't mean to have him do anything
for me
or chase him away.
I was just saying the pickles had gone bad
and might get him sick,
so we'd better serve him something better.
Couldn't you have finished your sentence?
But he left before I could finish it.
Who would've known
he was so stubborn?
Let's drop that topic.
I've heard
Longwan Logistics is in trouble.
Nothing serious.
Don't worry about it.
What will happen to you?
What can possibly happen to me?
Who would dare touch me?
Whoever comes after me
means he or she has a guilty conscience.
Right?
Take care of your leg.
Don't think about that.
What would you like to eat?
Don't bother considering.
I'll buy some pork trotters,
duck feet,
and chicken feet from the market
to make a soup that will help
with your recovery. Okay?
Fine. It's all up to you.
Alright?
It looks as if you're displeased.
Just wait here.
Okay.
Tianye,
you've been too busy to talk to me lately.
I'd hate to add to your burden.
I want to do something to support you.
We said we'd find time to talk,
but there has never been a right moment.
You've been coming home later and later.
My mind inevitably wanders
while I wait for you alone.
I can't help but worry about you.
At this rate,
I'll only make things worse for you.
I know you're hiding something from me.
But you wouldn't tell me anything.
In that case,
we should spend some time apart.
Let's wait till you settle
all issues at hand
before we discuss our problems.
Jiangyan,
have you seen Ziyi?
She said she'd stay at her brother's place
for a few days.
Did she not tell you?
She did.
She told me about it.
Tianye,
I want a word with you.
Come meet me at the old dock.
What can't you say to me at home?
Why come all the way to the dock?
Look.
Those deserted fishing boats are ours,
right?
Yes, the ones we used to fish with.
See,
these are paired with them.
I never imagined
that one day we the Longwan people
would discard our boats.
There are bigger vessels now.
It's normal...
for these to be phased out.
Yeah.
Everything changes.
Vessels change. People change.
Changes take place all the time,
right?
Nobody else is around.
Just speak your mind.
I'm just wondering,
if nothing had happened to my family
and that my parents were still alive,
what my life would be like,
besides being free of hatred.
What's done cannot be undone.
Fate...
is not to be changed.
But we can prevent
bad things from happening.
How?
I heard someone took
the company's financial records,
claiming it to be my order.
Whoever did that
must have his or her own reason.
For prevention, I suppose.
I just hate for all of us
to end up drifting apart.
I must protect the family
and Longwan...
in my own way.
[Public Security]
[Customs]
I've learned about all the matters
you've mentioned.
Madam Wen!
There are many cops outside.
Go take a look!
Cops?
Hurry up!
Maybe something's going on.
Hurry.
[Customs]
[Police]
Come on, open this box.
Who are you? What are you here for?
[Financial Office]
Come in.
[May Wealth Flow In]
[Search Warrent]
Hello.
We're anti-smuggling officers.
Please cooperate with our inspection.
[May Wealth Flow In]
No problem.
[Cold Storage]
[Restricted Area: Cold Storage.
No Trespassing]
What's inside?
Please open the door.
[Watch your step]
[Mind your hand]
Tianfei.
It's the last load, right?
Any driving permit on you?
Yes.
[Qunhuan Trading Co., Ltd.]
Dad.
I'm off to Uncle Tianfei's.
Wait. Where?
Uncle Tianfei's.
Why?
He has the latest gaming console at home.
I want to play it.
You can't go.
Why not?
Have you forgotten you got in trouble
in Longwan before?
You're never in luck there.
Is it because of the recent incident?
What have you heard?
It's all over the internet.
Don't believe that nonsense online.
People outside are just
jealous of our financial success. Got it?
Dad,
is everything okay?
It's adult business. Don't be nosy, kiddo.
Well,
what's the name
of that gaming console?
I'll buy you one
and play with you.
Alright, dinner's ready.
Let's go eat.
All you ever want is to go out and play.
Peng.
Did anything...
happen today?
No.
Just a routine inspection.
How are things between you
and Tianye?
Is everything okay?
Yes.
He's been busy lately, right?
He can't sleep well at night.
I can't either when the baby cries.
So I decided to stay a few days here.
Okay.
-Stay for as long as you like.
-Zhao Peng!
Zhao Peng!
Where's Zhao Peng?
Get back in.
Uncle.
-What's up?
-Zhao Peng.
My grandson told me
Longwan Logistics
is smuggling goods by water.
Is it true?
Zhao Peng, is the information online
true or false?
Yeah, Zhao Peng,
do you know something?
At least tell us what's really going on.
No, guys,
don't believe those rumors online.
There was just a routine inspection.
So all is fine?
Yes, all is fine.
When will the logistics company
resume operations?
Very soon.
Zhao Peng,
could it be the Longwan people
cooking up a scam?
Don't be deceived.
Or you'll end up suffering, right?
That's right.
Exactly.
If you're worried,
let me offer a solution.
If necessary,
we'll hold a villagers' meeting
to deliberate this matter
and the possibility
to stop working with them.
Now that all is fine,
there's no reason to quit. Right?
Right.
We should continue working with Longwan.
Tianye is good at making money.
That's right.
No, money shouldn't be our only focus.
If they lack development potential,
there's no point
in partnering with them,
right?
No, it's wrong.
When there are profits,
why leave a business partner?
Won't we be fools if we shrink
from the opportunity to make money?
Exactly.
You disagree with all my ideas.
Maybe I'm just not up for the job.
Then why not replace me
with someone else?
-No way.
-That won't do.
Zhao Peng,
this job must be yours.
Who else could take it if not you?
You must do it!
Yeah.
Zhao Peng,
Liu Tianye only trusts you.
How would we manage
without you?
Exactly!
You're entrusted
with Zhao Village's interests.
You can't just quit
after receiving some benefits.
Want to quit as you please?
That's not how it works.
Right, guys?
-Right!
-Exactly!
Zhao Peng,
a person should
follow through his commitments.
Understood?
Yes.
I get it.
Based on the maximum dividend ratio
set by your company,
[Longwan Logistics]
there couldn't be this much money
in the account.
Is it too much?
How come it seems too little to me?
What makes you say so?
We the Longwan people
value family ties above all.
Wenbo's father was my older brother.
[Longwan Logistics]
He died because of us.
So, we decided to set part
of our earnings aside for Wen Bo
and Mrs. Wen every time
dividends were distributed.
They deserve this 5 million,
or even 50 million,
if you ask me.
We owe them this much.
Thank you for taking the time
with my inquiry.
I should be the one thanking you.
I'm counting on you
for Wen Bo's matter.
No problem.
Ms. Leng,
will Longwan Logistics' case
affect Feng?
We'll conduct a thorough investigation
and draw a conclusion.
Personally speaking,
I trust Captain Qin.
So don't worry.
Good to hear that.
Has Feng mentioned
Xu Li's case to you?
Xu Li...
I know about her case.
It was the exact reason
for Feng's transfer
to Gutang Police Station.
Xu Li and I
grew up together as friends.
I went with her to file the police report.
Come to think of it,
Feng and I have known
each other for quite a long time.
He and his fellows,
in my opinion,
are excellent police officers—
more dedicated than most others.
But I guess Longwan Logistics' matter
has caused much distress to Feng.
Given that, I'd say he's somewhat
affected.
If something comes up,
I'll contact you again.
No need to see me out.
Okay.
Take care, Ms. Leng.
How's Baoying doing at your place
during these days?
He's doing great.
Ziyi's with him.
Don't worry.
What are Ziyi and Tianye planning to do?
I don't know either.
My sister
has always been strong-minded.
She doesn't share everything
with her family.
I...
will ask her when I get a chance.
If Ziyi is determined to get a divorce,
I won't object to it,
though I'm her mother-in-law.
I'll respect her decision.
You actually know better than anyone
about everything that has happened
between Ziyi and Tianye.
We used to
hold loads of grudges against each other.
It was the fight against Ma Jin
that brought our two villages together.
During those difficult times,
you chose to collaborate with us
and offered much help to us.
I've always kept all that in mind.
Those hard times are finally behind us.
Everyone has money now.
But...
do they really think...
that money was earned fair and square?
Zhao Peng,
why did you partner with Longwan
in the first place?
Wasn't it to improve the villagers' lives?
But look at what you guys are doing now.
Is it really for the villagers' benefit?
You're their leader.
If you lose your way,
the villagers will end up going astray
along with you.
I must set things straight.
A shareholders' meeting
will be held in a few days.
I hope to have your support.
Jiangyan.